

CLARISSA FATIMAH

clarissafatimah@gmail.com | https://www.linkedin.com/in/clarissafatimah/

An undergraduate student in Information Technology, who is highly passionate to expand experiences and knowledge. A well-rounded person who immensely believes in the future digitalization and currently has an interest in User-Centered Design and Renewable Energy field.

Education Level

Institut Teknologi Sepuluh Nopember Undergraduate in Information Technology, 3.70/4.00

Aug 2019 -

Work Experiences

Blibli.com - Indonesia Internship / UX Designer Aug 2021 - Feb 2022

- Contributed to managing and exploring the user experience in the Product Detail Page Squad, especially in product reviews.
- · Created the design needs to improve overall customer satisfaction including user journeys, wireframe, and prototyping.
- Planned the design initiatives for multiple stakeholders to identify business needs and drive product decisions.

Cyber Security and Smart City Laboratory ITS

Oct 2021 - Dec 2021

Database System Teaching Assistant

- Managed 70 students with projects and tasks in the Database system class.
- · Created a learning module using SQL Language.
- · Assess the students and ensure the deliverable task intelligibly.

Organisational Experience

Society Of Renewable Energy ITS

Oct 2021 - Present

Manager of Multimedia - Graphic Designer

- · Created the grand design during the management period.
- Managed a team of 5 visual and motion designers; Ensure deliverable tasks and fulfilled the visual design requests for the publication of events.
- Led the graphic design team in producing social media content and posted 45+ content during the management period
- Contributing to the organization's increase in Instagram followers count by 1,000+ in 6 months.

Himpunan Mahasiswa Teknologi Informasi

Mar 2021 - Dec 2021

Information media Secretary

- Contributes to the organization's achievement for being the 4th place in "Social Media Award" by BEM ITS.
- · Created the proposal event, such as "Developers Meet Design" and "Upgrading Staff HMIT".
- Developed and planned the division budgeting plan.

Skills, Achievements & Other Experience

- Achievements (2022): 1st Place in UI/UX Competition by Inforsary 9 (Politeknik Harapan Bersama Tegal)
- **Volunteer** (2021): As a Teaching Volunteer by Sobat Edukasi BEM FTEIC Educated the orphans about Ms. Word in Panti Asuhan BJ Habibie Keputih, Surabaya and Panti Asuhan Muhammadiyah Kenjeran, Surabaya.
- Event (2021): Head of Liaison Officer, ARA(A Renewal Agent) by HMIT Successfully gained participation rate beyond the target up to 14%
- Event (2021): Design Staff of Global Case Competition, International Youth Summit for Renewable Energy(IYSRE)
- Certification (2021): UI UX Bootcamp Sanbercode
- Certification (2021): Cloud Practioner Essentials Dicoding Indonesia
- Certification (2021): Architecting on AWS Dicoding Indonesia